Guide to the Naegele Outdoor Advertising records, 1978-2002 and undated RL.11324
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Naegele Outdoor Advertising records
1978-2002 and undated
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Naegele Advertising Companies (Minneapolis, Minn.)
John W. Hartman Center for Sales, Advertising & Marketing History
RL.11324
90.0 Linear Feet
Outdoor advertising firm founded as Naegele Outdoor Advertising in 1935 in Minneapolis, Minn. Renamed Fairway Outdoor 1991 and currently headquartered in Duncan, S.C. Includes billboard, painted display and poster designs, slides, photographs, printed materials and VHS videocassettes that document billboard locations, work in progress, corporate events, hurricane and storm damage and other aspects of the outdoor advertising industry. Many poster designs depict advertising for local North Carolina businesses. Acquired as part of the John W. Hartman Center for Sales, Advertising & Marketing History.
Arrangement
Arranged into the following series: Naegele Poster Designs; Fairway Poster Designs; Naegele Slides; Naegele Photographs; General Files; Audiovisual Materials.
Biographical / Historical
Outdoor advertising firm founded as Naegele Outdoor Advertising in 1935 in Minneapolis, Minn. Renamed Fairway Outdoor 1991 and currently headquartered in Duncan, S.C.
Founded by Robert O. Naegele 1935; acquired by Morris Communications 1985 and renamed Fairway Outdoor 1991; acquired by GTCR and Adams Outdoor 2015.
Access Restrictions
Collection is open for research. However, original audiovisual materials are closed until use copies can be produced.
Researchers must register and agree to copyright and privacy laws before using this collection.
All or portions of this collection may be housed off-site in Duke University's Library Service Center. The library may require up to 48 hours to retrieve these materials for research use.
Please contact Research Services staff before visiting the David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library to use this collection.
Provenance
The Naegele Outdoor Advertising records were received by the David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library as gift in 2002-2016.
Related Materials
Related materials may be found in the following Hartman Center Collections:
Outdoor Advertising Association of America (OAAA) Archives; OAAA Slide Library; OAAA Poster Designs; General Outdoor Advertising Company Plan Books; Wilkins Media Company records.
Collection Overview
Includes billboard, painted display and poster designs, slides, photographs, printed materials and VHS videocassettes that document billboard locations, work in progress, corporate events, hurricane and storm damage and other aspects of the outdoor advertising industry. Many poster designs depict advertising for local North Carolina businesses. Acquired as part of the John W. Hartman Center for Sales, Advertising & Marketing History.
Advertising, Outdoor; Billboards -- North Carolina; Advertising, Outdoor -- North Carolina; Fairway Outdoor Advertising; John W. Hartman Center for Sales, Advertising & Marketing History
- Naegele Poster Designs, 1981-1993 and undated; 1
  - 1-800-For-Baby, undated (Box 1)
  - 17 North Mini Warehouse, undated (Box 1)
  - 42nd Street Restaurant, 1986 (Box 1)
  - 63MFD (WMFD 630 AM), undated (Box 1)
  - 1-3GNI (WGNI), 1991 and undated; 3 folders (Box 1)
  - 1490 WWIL, undated (Box 1)
  - Abandoned Animals (New Hanover County Animal Control), undated (Box 1)
  - Abby Morton and Associates, undated (Box 77)
  - Adventure World, undated (Box 1)
  - AIDS "Feet" (Cape Fear Advertising Federation), 1990-1991 (Box 1)
  - Airlie Gardens, 1987 and undated; 2 folders (Box 1)
  - All in One Services, 1991 (Box 1)
  - Almost New Sales Center, 1991 (Box 1)
  - America PSA, undated; 2 folders (Box 2)
  - American Optometric Association, 1990 and undated; 2 folders (Box 2)
  - American Tourister, undated (Box 77)
  - Ann Miller, undated (Box 77)
  - Ann's Diamond Center, 1991 (Box 2)
  - Aquarium World, 1989 (Box 2)
  - Arby's/Video Views, undated (Box 2)
  - Artwork and photographs, various, 1987 and undated (Box 2)
  - Ashton Square, undated (Box 2)
  - Ask-a-Nurse, undated (Box 2)
  - Atlantic Coast Conservation Association, undated (Box 2)
  - Atlantic Towers, 1988-1992 and undated; 5 folders (Box 3)
  - The Atrium, undated (Box 3)
  - Auto Mall, undated (Box 85)
  - Azalea Festival, 1990 (Box 3)
  - Back to School, 1990 and undated (Box 3)
  - Bald Head Island, 1988-1989; 3 folders (Box 3)
  - Bald Head Island Ferry, undated (Box 3)
  - Bald Head Island Ferry, undated (Box 87)
  - Barbara Bigley Birthday, undated (Box 3)
  - Barnes Diamond Gallery, undated (Box 3)
  - Barnes Diamond Gallery, 1990 (Box 4)
  - Barnes Jewelers, undated (Box 77)
  - Battleship North Carolina, undated (Box 4)
  - Battleship North Carolina, undated; 2 folders (Box 77)
  - Beacon's Reach, undated (Box 4)
  - Beaufort House Restaurant, undated (Box 4)
  - Beech Nut Chewing Tobacco, undated (Box 4)
  - Before Drugs--After Drugs, undated (Box 4)
  - Belk, 1985-1992 and undated; 9 folders (Box 4)
  - Belk, 1989-1991; 2 folders (Box 77)
  - Belvedere Plantation, undated (Box 4)
  - Ben Franklin Stores, undated (Box 5)
  - Best Western/Denny's, 1989 and undated (Box 5)
  - Bexley/Howell Building and Realty, undated (Box 5)
  - BHI, undated (Box 5)
  - Big Daddy's, undated (Box 5)
  - Big and Tall, 1989 (Box 5)
  - Birthday: Bobby Jordan 40th, undated (Box 5)
  - Bland and Associates, undated (Box 5)
  - Block N.C. Senate campaign, undated (Box 5)
  - Bob Jordan for Lt. Governor, undated (Box 5)
  - Bob King Automall, 1990-1991 and undated; 8 folders (Box 5)
  - Bob King Pontiac, undated (Box 5)
  - Bogue Inlet Pier, 1990-1992; 2 folders (Box 6)
  - Bogue Inlet Pier/Beachfront RV Park, 1992 (Box 6)
  - Bosch, 1988 and undated; 3 folders (Box 6)
  - Boseman's Sporting Goods, undated (Box 6)
  - Boy Scouts, calendars, 1983-1985 (Box 87)
  - Boyd Honda & Toyota, 1991 (Box 6)
  - Boyd/Charles, 1991 (Box 6)
  - Bruno's Restaurant, 1991 (Box 6)
  - Bryan Foods/Wilson's, undated (Box 6)
  - Budweiser, 1987-1988; 3 folders (Box 6)
  - Budweiser, 1991 and undated; 16 folders (Box 7)
  - Budweiser, undated (Box 8)
  - Budweiser, 1985-1991; 3 folders (Box 77)
  - Budweiser, undated; 5 folders (Box 78)
  - Bushwackers, 1988 (Box 8)
  - Butch Gentry RE/Max, 1992 and undated; 2 folders (Box 8)
  - Cadillac, 1984-1986 (Box 8)
  - Call-1 Call, 1991 (Box 8)
  - Cameron Barkley, 1989-1990 and undated; 2 folders (Box 8)
  - Cancer Society, 1983-1986 and undated; 2 folders (Box 8)
  - Canon, 1993 (Box 8)
  - Cantina East, 1991 (Box 8)
  - The Cape, undated; 4 folders (Box 8)
  - Cape Fear Advertising Federation, 1988 and undated; 2 folders (Box 8)
  - Cape Fear Advertising Federation, undated (Box 78)
  - Cape Fear Memorial Hospital, 1991 (Box 8)
  - Capps Printing/Herald Printing/Eastern Printing, undated (Box 8)
  - Car Audio Concepts, 1989 (Box 8)
  - Cardinal Motors, 1992 and undated; 4 folders (Box 9)
  - Caribbean Trading Co., 1986 (Box 9)
  - Carl Johnson Audi, 1985-1986 and undated; 4 folders (Box 9)
  - Carnival Cruise Lines, undated (Box 9)
  - Carobell Children's Home, 1990 (Box 9)
  - Carolina Hatteras, 1988 and undated; 2 folders (Box 9)
  - Carolina Pines, undated (Box 10)
  - Carolina Pottery, undated (Box 10)
  - Carolina Princess, 1987 and undated; 2 folders (Box 10)
  - Carriage Hills, undated (Box 10)
  - Carteret Co. Chamber of Commerce, undated (Box 10)
  - Cash-a-Check, undated; 2 folders (Box 10)
  - Caswell Beach Plantation, undated (Box 10)
  - Caswell Dunes, undated; 4 folders (Box 10)
  - Cedar Point Tire/Firestone, undated; 2 folders (Box 10)
  - Cedar Tree, undated; 2 folders (Box 10)
  - Cellular One, undated (Box 11)
  - Centel Cellular, undated; 2 folders (Box 11)
  - Center for Alternative Programs of Education, undated (Box 11)
  - Charleston Place, undated (Box 11)
  - Chuck E. Cheese, undated (Box 11)
  - Clayton Homes, undated (Box 11)
  - Clipper, 1988-1993; 3 folders (Box 78)
  - Club 108, undated (Box 11)
  - Coastal Car Stereo, undated (Box 11)
  - Coastal Carolina Community College, 1990 (Box 11)
  - Coastal Dry Cleaners, 1990 (Box 11)
  - Coastal Floors, undated; 2 folders (Box 11)
  - Coastal Oldsmobile Toyota, undated (Box 11)
  - Coke, undated (Box 11)
  - Coors Light, undated (Box 11)
  - Core Sound, 1990-1991 (Box 11)
  - Corporal Garreth C. Isaak memorial, undated (Box 11)
  - Coquina Harbour, undated; 2 folders (Box 12)
  - The Cotton Exchange, 1987 (Box 12)
  - Craft American Hardware, undated (Box 12)
  - Crimestoppers, undated (Box 12)
  - Cracker's Marine, 1988-1989 and undated; 3 folders (Box 12)
  - Crowder and Company, 1990 (Box 12)
  - Crystal Coast Diving Adventure, 1988 (Box 12)
  - C&S Paint, 1992 and undated; 2 folders (Box 12)
  - C&S Paint, undated (Box 79)
  - C.S. Rolle Insurance, undated; 2 folders (Box 12)
  - The Daily News, 1991 (Box 13)
  - Days Inn, 1991-1992 and undated; 8 folders (Box 13)
  - Delta, undated (Box 79)
  - Doctor's In Immediate Care, undated (Box 13)
  - Domino's Pizza, 1985-1988; 6 folders (Box 13)
  - Domino's Pizza, 1988-1992 and undated; 9 folders (Box 14)
  - Domino's Pizza, undated; 6 folders (Box 15)
  - Domino's Pizza, undated; 2 folders (Box 79)
  - Don Kimball Chevrolet, 1984; 3 folders (Box 15)
  - Don Kimball Chevrolet, 1985-1986 and undated; 8 folders (Box 16)
  - Don Kimball Chevrolet, undated; 3 folders (Box 17)
  - Don Kimball dealerships, undated; 3 folders (Box 79)
  - Downtown Wilmington Association, 1989 (Box 17)
  - Downtown Wilmington Shopping, undated (Box 17)
  - D. West Jewelers, undated (Box 17)
  - Earth Day Alliance, 1990 (Box 17)
  - East Carolina Honda Volvo, 1988 and undated; 2 folders (Box 80)
  - East Carolina Honda Volvo, undated; 2 folders (Box 85)
  - East Carolina University Basketball, 1991-1992 (Box 17)
  - Eastern Carolina Forestry Festival, 1990 (Box 17)
  - Eastern Petroleum, undated (Box 17)
  - Eastover Trading Co., undated (Box 17)
  - Echo Farms, 1987 (Box 17)
  - Eckerd, undated (Box 80)
  - Edgeworth, 1991 (Box 17)
  - Edward's Fine Dining, undated (Box 17)
  - El Berta Motor Inn, 1991 and undated; 2 folders (Box 17)
  - Emerald Gold, 1991; 2 folders (Box 17)
  - Emerald Gold, 1991 and undated; 2 folders (Box 80)
  - Emerald Plantation, undated (Box 18)
  - Empire Mine, undated (Box 18)
  - Erase Illiteracy PSA, 1991-1992 (Box 80)
  - Etheridge Furniture, 1993; 2 folders (Box 18)
  - Eve Cigarettes, 1991 (Box 18)
  - Everhart Nissan, 1989 (Box 18)
  - Eye Care Center, undated (Box 18)
  - Eye Catchers, undated (Box 18)
  - Fayetteville Chamber of Commerce, 1991 (Box 19)
  - Financial institutions, 1988 (Box 19)
  - First Citizens Bank, 1989 and undated; 4 folders (Box 19)
  - First Citizens Bank, undated (Box 80)
  - First Union, undated; 2 folders (Box 19)
  - Fish Crossing Ahead, undated (Box 19)
  - Fisherman's Galley, undated (Box 19)
  - Fisherman's Wharf, 1990 and undated; 3 folders (Box 20)
  - Flagship Seafood Restaurant, undated (Box 20)
  - Fleischman's clothiers, 1989 and undated; 3 folders (Box 20)
  - Food Service Inc. logo, undated (Box 87)
  - Foster's Manufactured Housing, undated (Box 20)
  - Fountain Tire Service, 1988 and undated; 3 folders (Box 20)
  - Fox Network, undated (Box 20)
  - Fox Run Farm, undated (Box 20)
  - Fran's Gifts and Beachwear, 1992 and undated; 3 folders (Box 21)
  - Frazier's Seafood, Steak and Lobster, undated (Box 21)
  - Frazier's Seafood, Steak and Lobster; 980 WAAV; Olde Point; Medico Urgent Care Clinic; Albert F. Rhodes Fine Jewelry, 1985 and undated (Box 21)
  - Furniture Fair, 1989 and undated; 3 folders (Box 21)
  - The Furniture Patch, undated (Box 21)
  - Gary Trawick for Superior Court Judge, undated (Box 21)
  - Gayle Humphries Day Care, undated (Box 21)
  - Gentry House/Hugo Boss, 1990 and undated; 4 folders (Box 21)
  - Gentry House/Hugo Boss, undated (Box 80)
  - George L. Jones for Mayor, 1987 (Box 22)
  - The Gingham Basket, undated (Box 22)
  - Give Us a Whirl, undated (Box 22)
  - Golden Corral, undated (Box 22)
  - Golden Corral, undated (Box 85)
  - Golden East Crossing, undated (Box 22)
  - Golfin' Dolphin, 1993 (Box 22)
  - Greater Wilmington Chamber of Commerce, undated; 2 folders (Box 22)
  - Green Tree Inn/Yellow Rose Saloon, undated (Box 22)
  - Greenville Toyota, undated (Box 22)
  - Grocery stores, Harris Teeter and others, undated (Box 22)
  - Guiseppe's, 1988 (Box 22)
  - Gumbranch Square, undated (Box 22)
  - Guthrie Farms, undated (Box 22)
  - Hampton Inn, 1988 and undated; 4 folders (Box 22)
  - Handy Helpers, undated (Box 22)
  - Harvey's, undated; 2 folders (Box 22)
  - Hastings Ford, 1991 (Box 22)
  - Head for Good Times, undated (Box 80)
  - Henrietta II River Cruises, undated (Box 22)
  - Hidden Harbor/Jonaquin's Landing, undated (Box 23)
  - Hieronymous Seafood Restaurant, undated; 2 folders (Box 23)
  - Hieronymous Seafood Restaurant, undated (Box 80)
  - Hill's, 1987 (Box 23)
  - Hills Discount Pharmacy, undated (Box 23)
  - Hilton Inn, undated (Box 23)
  - Holden Beach, undated (Box 23)
  - Holden Beach Realty, undated (Box 23)
  - Holden Beach Realty, undated (Box 87)
  - Holiday Chrysler Plymouth, undated (Box 23)
  - Holiday Inn, undated; 4 folders (Box 23)
  - Holiday Inn Jacksonville, undated (Box 87)
  - Holiday Tral-L-Park, undated (Box 23)
  - Holloway Inn, undated (Box 23)
  - Home Insulation Co., undated (Box 23)
  - Howard's Furniture, 1991 (Box 23)
  - Howard's Furniture, undated (Box 24)
  - Human Relations Month, 1990 and undated; 3 folders (Box 24)
  - Humane Society, 1990 (Box 24)
  - Humphry Heating and Cooling, undated (Box 24)
  - Hunter's Creek, undated (Box 24)
  - Idea Exchange, various designs, 1988 and undated; 3 folders (Box 24)
  - Idea layouts, undated (Box 24)
  - IGA, undated (Box 24)
  - Independence Mall, 1986-1991; 5 folders (Box 24)
  - Independence Mall, undated; 2 folders (Box 25)
  - Indigo Plantation, 1987 and undated; 3 folders (Box 25)
  - Infant Care, undated; 2 folders (Box 25)
  - Inland Harbor, undated; 2 folders (Box 25)
  - Inlet Inn, 1985 (Box 25)
  - Inlet Watch Yacht Club, 1990 (Box 25)
  - Intracoastal Realty, 1989 and undated; 2 folders (Box 25)
  - Island North, undated (Box 25)
  - Island North, 1985 (Box 80)
  - Island of Lights, undated (Box 25)
  - Island of Lights, undated (Box 26)
  - Jackson Beverage/Budweiser, 1990 (Box 26)
  - Jackson Beverage Company, undated (Box 80)
  - Jackson's Big Oak Barbecue, undated (Box 26)
  - Jacksonville Birthing Center, 1992; 2 folders (Box 26)
  - Jacksonville Manufactured Housing Association, 1985 (Box 80)
  - Jacksonville Speedway, undated (Box 26)
  - James Sprunt Technical College, 1984-1985 and undated; 4 folders (Box 26)
  - Jay Taylor Exterminating Co., undated (Box 26)
  - Jay Taylor Exterminating Co., undated; 2 folders (Box 81)
  - Jedco Construction, 1988-1989; 4 folders (Box 26)
  - Jedco Construction, 1989-1990 and undated; 4 folders (Box 27)
  - Jedco Construction, 1988 (Box 81)
  - Jensen's Coastal Plantation, 1986 (Box 27)
  - Jeter's Gourmet Hot Dogs, undated (Box 27)
  - J.H. Croaker Co., 1988 (Box 27)
  - Jill Casey Welcome Home, 1985 (Box 27)
  - Joe Alcoke dealerships, 1986-1987; 3 folders (Box 27)
  - Joe Alcoke dealerships, 1987-1991 and undated; 12 folders (Box 28)
  - Joe Alcoke dealerships, undated (Box 81)
  - John Codington for N.C. Senate, undated; 2 folders (Box 29)
  - John Crossland Company, undated; 2 folders (Box 29)
  - John's Creek, undated (Box 29)
  - John's Creek, undated (Box 81)
  - Jones (retail), undated; 2 folders (Box 29)
  - Jones Brothers Marine, undated (Box 29)
  - Jones Enterprises, undated; 2 folders (Box 29)
  - Josh Allen Apparel, undated (Box 29)
  - Journey's Restaurant, 1991 (Box 29)
  - J.R. Dun Jewelers, undated; 2 folders (Box 30)
  - Jubilee Park, undated; 5 folders (Box 30)
  - Jungleland, undated (Box 30)
  - Jungleland, undated (Box 81)
  - Jungle Rapids, 1988 and undated; 2 folders (Box 30)
  - Justin's Women's Wear, 1988 and undated; 2 folders (Box 30)
  - K&W Cafeteria, undated (Box 85)
  - Kanki Japanese House of Steak, undated; 2 folders (Box 30)
  - The KAT 103 FM, undated (Box 30)
  - Katia Italian Cuisine, undated (Box 31)
  - Kennedy GMC, undated (Box 31)
  - Kennedy Oldsmobile, 1984-1985 (Box 81)
  - Kentucky Fried Chicken, undated (Box 81)
  - Kids' Don't Use Drugs PSA, undated (Box 31)
  - Kimball-Leith Auto Village, undated (Box 31)
  - Kiwanis Club of Wilmington, 1986 (Box 31)
  - Knock on Wood, undated (Box 31)
  - K-Mart, 1988 (Box 31)
  - Kure Beach Club, undated; 4 folders (Box 31)
  - Lady's in Waiting, undated (Box 31)
  - Lake Shore Commons, undated (Box 31)
  - Landfall, undated (Box 31)
  - LeJeune Motors, 1983-1987 and undated; 3 folders (Box 31)
  - LeJeune Motors, 1986-1987 (Box 32)
  - LeJeune Motors, 1983-1987; 4 folders (Box 81)
  - Leland Hardware/True Value, undated (Box 32)
  - Lens Crafters, undated (Box 32)
  - L&M Pizza, undated; 3 folders (Box 32)
  - Locals Only, undated (Box 82)
  - Loggerhead development, undated (Box 32)
  - Long Leaf Mall, 1986 and undated; 5 folders (Box 32)
  - Lord Carteret Motor Inn, undated; 2 folders (Box 32)
  - Lost Creek Café and Lounge, undated (Box 33)
  - Lube Center, undated; 2 folders (Box 33)
  - Magnolia Plantation, undated (Box 33)
  - Mai Tai Restaurant, 1992 (Box 33)
  - Mallard Creek, undated (Box 33)
  - Maps, undated (Box 33)
  - Marine deakerships, 1985-1988; 3 folders (Box 33)
  - Marino's Subs and Pizza, undated (Box 82)
  - Mark Walker Humphrey anti-drug PSA, undated (Box 33)
  - Marketplace Mall, undated; 7 folders (Box 33)
  - Marketplace Mall, undated (Box 34)
  - Marketplace Mall, undated (Box 82)
  - Marsh Landing, 1990 (Box 34)
  - Massey dealerships, 1991 and undated; 2 folders (Box 34)
  - Master Tech, undated (Box 34)
  - Maurice Williams and the Zodiacs, 1988 (Box 34)
  - Mazda of Jacksonville, NC, undated (Box 82)
  - McDonald's, 1989 and undated; 7 folders (Box 34)
  - McDonald's/Toys for Tots, undated; 2 folders (Box 34)
  - McDonald's/Toys for Tots/USMC, 1991 (Box 82)
  - McKensie Supply Company, undated; 2 folders (Box 34)
  - MCQueen & Associates, undated (Box 34)
  - Medico Urgent Care Clinic, undated (Box 34)
  - Medico Urgent Care Clinic, undated (Box 82)
  - Mercury, 1986 (Box 35)
  - Michael Mills for N.C. House, 1992; 3 folders (Box 35)
  - Michelin, undated (Box 35)
  - Military Law Center, undated (Box 35)
  - Military Law Center, undated (Box 85)
  - Miller Beer, 1989 (Box 35)
  - Miller/United Cerebral Palsy, 1989 (Box 35)
  - Miss North Carolina, undated (Box 35)
  - Mix 97.3/Bob King, undated (Box 35)
  - Mix 96, 1991 (Box 36)
  - Monitor Motor Inn, undated (Box 36)
  - Moore Buick, 1989-1990 and undated; 4 folders (Box 36)
  - Moore Buick, undated (Box 87)
  - Moore's Barbecue, undated; 2 folders (Box 36)
  - Morningside at the Park, 1987 (Box 36)
  - Muffler and Engine Xpress, undated; 3 folders (Box 36)
  - Murray Memorial Baptist Church, 1993 (Box 36)
  - Murray Memorial Baptist Church, undated (Box 82)
  - NAACP Wilmington, undated (Box 36)
  - Naegele miscellaneous, 1985-1988 and undated; 2 folders (Box 36)
  - Naegele miscellaneous, 1990 and undated; 10 folders (Box 37)
  - Naegele miscellaneous, 1990 (Box 82)
  - National Child Safety Council, 1986 (Box 37)
  - National Dodge, 1991 and undated; 2 folders (Box 37)
  - National Outlet, undated (Box 37)
  - National Outlet, undated; 3 folders (Box 38)
  - Nautilus Fitness Center, undated (Box 38)
  - Nectar, undated (Box 38)
  - Neuse Sport Shop, 1990 (Box 38)
  - Neuwirth Hyundai, 1990; 2 folders (Box 38)
  - New Hanover County Art Contest, 1990-1991 (Box 38)
  - New Hanover County Fair, 1986-1990 and undated; 3 folders (Box 38)
  - New Hanover County Health Department, 1990 (Box 38)
  - New Hanover County Health Department, undated (Box 85)
  - New Hanover County Sestbelt Coalition, 1991 (Box 82)
  - New Hanover County Schools, 1990; 2 folders (Box 38)
  - New Hanover County Schools, 1990 (Box 82)
  - New Hanover International Airport, undated (Box 38)
  - New River Shopping Center, 1990-1992; 3 folders (Box 38)
  - New River Shopping Center, undated; 5 folders (Box 39)
  - Noah's Ark, undated; 2 folders (Box 39)
  - Noriega political design, 1990 (Box 39)
  - North Carolina Aquarium, 1988 and undated; 2 folders (Box 39)
  - North Carolina Elks, undated (Box 39)
  - North Carolina Equity, undated (Box 39)
  - North Carolina Museum of History, 1991 (Box 39)
  - North Carolina Sportsman's Show, 1990 (Box 39)
  - North Carolina Wildlife and Sportsman's Show, undated (Box 39)
  - North Carolina Zoo, 1990 (Box 82)
  - North Wilmington Chiropractic, 1991-1992; 2 folders (Box 39)
  - Northchase development, 1989 (Box 39)
  - Northchase development, undated; 2 folders (Box 40)
  - Northgate Mall, 1991-1992; 2 folders (Box 40)
  - Northside development, 1988 (Box 40)
  - Northwest Creek Marina, 1992 (Box 40)
  - Ocean Lakes development, 1984 (Box 40)
  - Odyssey night club, undated; 2 folders (Box 40)
  - Oh! Brian's, undated (Box 40)
  - Olympics, 1984 and undated (Box 40)
  - Onslow County Commissioners, undated (Box 40)
  - "Outdoor Image", undated (Box 40)
  - Outdoor Advertising Association of America Image Promotion Contest, 1988 (Box 40)
  - Outdoor Equipment Company, undated (Box 40)
  - "Outsells All the Other 146 Firms", undated (Box 40)
  - Pak-a-Sak Food Stores, undated; 3 folders (Box 41)
  - Parade of Homes, undated (Box 41)
  - Paradise Tower, undated; 4 folders (Box 41)
  - Parkwood Mall, 1990 (Box 41)
  - Parrish Caine brake service, undated; 2 folders (Box 41)
  - Pawn USA, undated (Box 41)
  - Pedal Pushers, 1987 (Box 41)
  - Peele Homes, undated; 2 folders (Box 41)
  - Pepsi, 1988-1991 and undated; 4 folders (Box 41)
  - Pet-Go-Round, undated (Box 42)
  - Pfizer, 1988 (Box 42)
  - P&G Body Shop, 1991 (Box 42)
  - Pickett & Bowles Mortuary, undated (Box 42)
  - Pier 20 Seafood Restaurant, undated; 5 folders (Box 42)
  - Pirate Island Theme Park, undated (Box 42)
  - Pizza City, 1988 (Box 42)
  - Pizza Hut, 1987 (Box 42)
  - Pizza Hut, 1992 (Box 85)
  - The Plaza, 1991 (Box 42)
  - Pollard's IGA, 1987 (Box 42)
  - Pollard's IGA, undated; 3 folders (Box 43)
  - Porter's Neck Plantation and Country Club, 1991 and undated; 3 folders (Box 83)
  - Posturepedic, undated (Box 43)
  - Professional Carpets, undated (Box 43)
  - Professional Uniform and Shoe Centers, 1987 (Box 43)
  - Pro-Line, 1987 (Box 43)
  - The Psychiatric Program of Duplin General Hospital, 1987 (Box 43)
  - Pulte Master Builder, undated (Box 44)
  - Ramada Inn, 1992 and undated; 2 folders (Box 44)
  - Rape Crisis Center, undated (Box 44)
  - "Read to Us" PSA, undated (Box 44)
  - Real Estate Preview, 1989 and undated; 2 folders (Box 44)
  - "Recycle" PSA, undated (Box 44)
  - "Red" Daugherty Real Estate, undated (Box 44)
  - Reed's Jewelers, undated (Box 44)
  - Referee photographs, undated (Box 85)
  - Regal Florist, 1989 (Box 44)
  - The Rental Agency, 1990 (Box 44)
  - Rentoco Equipment Service, undated (Box 45)
  - Rippy Cadillac, 1992 (Box 45)
  - Rippy Cadillac, undated (Box 83)
  - Rippy-King Mitsubishi, undated; 2 folders (Box 45)
  - Ronald McDonald House, undated (Box 45)
  - Rose Brothers Furniture, undated (Box 45)
  - Roth, Roth and Steinberg, undated (Box 45)
  - Rouse-Watson Real Estate, 1989 and undated; 3 folders (Box 45)
  - Rucker Johns Restaurant, undated (Box 45)
  - Sam Lawson Car Sales, undated; 2 folders (Box 46)
  - Sanco developers, undated; 2 folders (Box 46)
  - Sander's Ford, undated (Box 46)
  - Sandpiper Seafood House, undated (Box 46)
  - Sands Investments, undated (Box 46)
  - Schlitz, undated (Box 85)
  - Seahawks (UNC Wilmington), 1989-1990; 5 folders (Box 46)
  - Sears, 1990 and undated; 2 folders (Box 46)
  - Seat Belts PSA, undated (Box 46)